<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WUMap_NOV_15</string>
    <string name="soft_dark_blue">#4175aa</string>
    <string-array name="bldg_names">
        <item>Art Building (AB)</item>
        <item>Bennett Hall (BT)</item>
        <item>Benton Hall (BE)</item>
        <item>Bradbury Thompson Alumni Center</item>
        <item>Carnegie Hall</item>
        <item>Garvey</item>
        <item>Henderson Commons (HC)</item>
        <item>KBI Building</item>
        <item>Law School ()</item>
        <item>Lee Arena</item>
        <item>Mabee Library</item>
        <item>Memorial Union</item>
        <item>Morgan Hall (MO)</item>
        <item>Mulvane Museum</item>
        <item>Petro</item>
        <item>Stoffer Hall (ST)</item>
        <item>Washburn University Foundation</item>
        <item>White Concert Hall</item>
        <item>Yager Stadium</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="bldg_desc">
        <item>The Art Building (AB) - The Art Department is located in the Art Building.</item>
        <item>Bennett Hall (BT) - Information Technology Services is located in Bennett Hall. Need
            to reset your password? Visit BT104.
        </item>
        <item>Benton Hall (BE) - Home to the School of Applied Studies which includes Criminal
            Justice and Social Work.
        </item>
        <item>Bradbury Thompson Alumni Center - Located on Washburn’s campus off 17th and Jewell,
            the Bradbury Thompson Alumni Center sits across the street from White Concert Hall and
            Mulvane Art Museum. The facility is designed to serve the needs of alumni, the university and the Topeka community.</item>
        <item>Carnegie Hall -</item>
        <item>Garvey - Home of the Theatre and Music Departments.</item>
        <item>Henderson Commons (HC) - Home to the School of Business as well as History, Political
            Science, Psychology and Sociology/Anthropology.
        </item>
        <item>KBI Building - Kansas Bureau of Investigation</item>
        <item>Law Building - Home to the School of Law.</item>
        <item>Lee Arena -</item>
        <item>Mabee Library - Mabee Library is located in the center of campus between
            Moore Bowl/Yager Stadium and Henderson Learning Resources Center. The
            ibrary was completed during the 1977-78 school year and named in honor of
            J.E. and L.E. Mabee of Oklahoma. Before their deaths, Mr. and Mrs. Mabee
            established a foundation to provide money for educational and religious
            institutions in the Midwest region. Washburn University applied for and
            received a grant from the Mabee Foundation to build a new library during
            the rebuilding phase after the 1966 tornado, which destroyed numerous
            buildings and damaged many others. - From: "A Brief History of the Washburn University Libraries" By Martha Imparato, University Archivist</item>
        <item>The Memorial Union - A great place to study or relax, and get some food.</item>
        <item>Morgan Hall (MO) - The home to Math and English as well as the president\'s office,
            the various Dean\'s Offices, and many other administrative offices.</item>
        <item>Mulvane Museum - </item>
        <item>Petro</item>
        <item>Stoffer Hall (ST) - Home to Biology, Chemistry, Computer Information Sciences and
            Physics.</item>
        <item>Washburn University Foundation- Working collaboratively with Washburn
            University, the Washburn University Foundation, as the designated alumni
            relations, fundraising, and gift-stewardship organization for Washburn
            University, is committed to leading and coordinating the efforts to expand
            the University’s base of volunteer support and engagement and private
            financial support.</item>
        <item>White Concert Hall - </item>
        <item>Yager Stadium - The football and soccer fields.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="bldg_x">
        <item>.51904f</item>
        <item>.69328f</item>
        <item>.36358f</item>
        <item>.32700f</item>
        <item>.67000f</item>
        <item>.46000f</item>
        <item>.37899f</item>
        <item>.88500f</item>
        <item>.17928f</item>
        <item>.75000f</item>
        <item>.46400f</item>
        <item>.45270f</item>
        <item>.54290f</item>
        <item>.40000f</item>
        <item>.75500f</item>
        <item>.78308f</item>
        <item>.04800f</item>
        <item>.41000f</item>
        <item>.57900f</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="bldg_y">
        <item>.61538f</item>
        <item>.20090f</item>
        <item>.38483f</item>
        <item>.11600f</item>
        <item>.29000f</item>
        <item>.15000f</item>
        <item>.47031f</item>
        <item>.62000f</item>
        <item>.24490f</item>
        <item>.48000f</item>
        <item>.45800f</item>
        <item>.28000f</item>
        <item>.18010f</item>
        <item>.18000f</item>
        <item>.40000f</item>
        <item>.16317f</item>
        <item>.19000f</item>
        <item>.12000f</item>
        <item>.48500f</item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="bldg_photos">
        <item>@drawable/art</item>
        <item>@drawable/bennett</item>
        <item>@drawable/benton</item>
        <item>@drawable/bradbury</item>
        <item>@drawable/carnegie</item>
        <item>@drawable/garvey</item>
        <item>@drawable/henderson</item>
        <item>@drawable/kbi</item>
        <item>@drawable/law</item>
        <item>@drawable/lee</item>
        <item>@drawable/mabee</item>
        <item>@drawable/memorial</item>
        <item>@drawable/morgan</item>
        <item>@drawable/mulvane</item>
        <item>@drawable/petro</item>
        <item>@drawable/stoffer</item>
        <item>@drawable/foundation</item>
        <item>@drawable/white</item>
        <item>@drawable/yager</item>
    </integer-array>
    <string-array name="dept_names">
        <item>Allied Health</item>
        <item>Art (AR)</item>
        <item>Biology (BI)</item>
        <item>Chemistry (CH)</item>
        <item>Communication Studies</item>
        <item>Computer Information Sciences (CIS)</item>
        <item>Criminal Justice (CJ)</item>
        <item>Education (ED)</item>
        <item>English (EN)</item>
        <item>History (HI)</item>
        <item>Human Services</item>
        <item>Kinesiology</item>
        <item>Mass Media</item>
        <item>Mathematics (MA)</item>
        <item>Modern Languages</item>
        <item>Music</item>
        <item>Philosophy and Religious Studies</item>
        <item>Physics and Astronomy</item>
        <item>Political Science and Public Administration</item>
        <item>Psychology</item>
        <item>Social Work</item>
        <item>Sociology/Anthropology (SO/AN)</item>
        <item>Theatre</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="dept_desc">
        <item>The Allied Health Department is located in room 107 of Benton 107.</item>
        <item>The Art Department is located in the Art Building. Stop by sometime and see works by
            students and faculty on display here.
        </item>
        <item>The Biology Department is located in room 202 of Stoffer Hall.</item>
        <item>The Chemistry Department is located in room 312 of Stoffer Hall.</item>
        <item>The Communication Department is located in room 206 of Morgan.</item>
        <item>The CIS Department is located in room 304 of Stoffer Hall.</item>
        <item>The Criminal Justice Department is located in Benton 201.</item>
        <item>The Education Department is located in room 202 of Carnegie.</item>
        <item>The English Department is located in room 237 of Morgan.</item>
        <item>The History Department is located in room 211 of Henderson.</item>
        <item>The Human Services is located in room 211 of Benton.</item>
        <item>The Kinesiology Department is located in room 201 of Petro.</item>
        <item>The Mass Media Department is located in room 311 of Henderson.</item>
        <item>The Mathematics Department is located in room 250 of Morgan.</item>
        <item>The Modern Language Department is located in room 250 of Morgan.</item>
        <item>The Music Department is located in room 211 of Garvey.</item>
        <item>The Philosophy and Religious Studies Department is located in room 206 of Morgan.
        </item>
        <item>The Physics and Astronomy Department is located in room 211 of Stoffer.</item>
        <item>The Political Science and Public Administration Department is located in room 215
            Henderson.
        </item>
        <item>The Psychology Department is located in room 211 of Henderson.</item>
        <item>The Social Work Department is located in room 412 in Benton.</item>
        <item>The Department of Sociology and Anthropology is located in room 211 of Henderson
        </item>
        <item>The Theatre Department is located in Garvey</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="serve_names">
        <item>Student Health Center</item>
        <item>University Police</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="serve_desc">
        <item>Located in Morgan Hall.</item>
        <item>Located in Morgan Hall.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
